A forest tiger.
And if I'm not wrong, this is...
a flower fairy.
But not from this area.
Where could she come from?
You'll never get me!
Bite!
Not me...
I let you run now!
What on earth did she want here?
Piyu!
Flower fairy
You can't devour everything!
You can eat only wood, you know?
She says you can't eat everything.
Only wood.
Okay!
The news of the Sky Pearl have already spread.
How do you know?
It's already on the website.
Website?
Yeah.
It's only used by spirits.
Humans can't reach it.
There's such a thing?
Many spirits live in the human world.
Members here are just a few of them.
It's so not the way I thought...
The human world affects spirits quite much.
This is a member-only board.
It has about 3000 members,
but it's quite lively.
Books of Vows
Look, it's here that the Sky Pearl quest was accomplished.
I can't read well.
Sky Pearl quest was accomplished
Laozi
NC
Holy crap, someone did this?!
I've never thought this can be done!
Is this still your profile picture...?
Laozi!!!
Respect to the great deity!
How's Diting doing?
This was posted by Master Lao.
Does he have to post it?
Yes, it's the rule.
Vow quests are well-known in the spirit community.
There are even manuals for them.
Manuals?
Yeah, because the originals are complicated.
Look. They were published after
Master Lao stopped making vows.
Book of Vows 7
Complete Collection of
Books of Vows
Collection of Twelve
(complete)
Compass to the
Collection of Twelve
(Blue Creek version)
Experiences of
Quest-Doers
These You Should Do Again:
Quests to Revisit
Unaccomplished
Quests
Simple Quests
Book of Vows 3
Book of Vows (old)
There are 12 books of vows without the manuals.
Together the Collection of Twelve.
So many of them...
Many people follow these posts.
You see my point?
You mean...
someone can take the prize away?
Exactly.
It's easier than to go to Master Lao's.
Isn't this the fairy from yesterday?
What do you want here?
You'll never know! Kill me if you want!
Okay.
Spare me, my lord.
I'm looking for a cure for my friend.
I felt the movement of special spirit force here.
Fairy sense!
It's quite a rare skill.
What's this?
My name is Fenmo.
I'm a lovely little flower fairy.
I don't harm people.
Don't worry.
We are spirits too.
Why didn't you say so?
But I'm human.
Good morning.
I'm a lovely little flower fairy...
What's wrong with your friend?
He's gravely ill.
He's fast asleep and won't wake up.
So this is why you came?
I see...
But the thing you felt can't cure illnesses.
You could take me to your friend.
Maybe I can help him.
Really?
Soul Wind Mountain?
It's a long way from here.
No wonder I've never met you.
Have you found anything?
Some de-souling grass.
I don't think it helps here.
We can go there right now.
A fairy dragon...
So there are fairies that big around here...
He can't take us all.
You should wait us here.
We'll be back soon.
Should I put Piyu in his cage?
It's okay.
Mr. Piyu will be a good boy.
Be good, no roughhousing.
No need to say so.
Here's a Heishu to keep an eye on him.
Hey!
Thanks for helping us out, Xiaolong.
Unconscious for a month?
Is he a flower fairy too?
No, he's a tree fairy.
How can a fairy be in a coma for such a long time?
It's strange.
Stop! This is the place!
Qiguo!
This way!
Xiaolong, you can go back now.
I'll call you when we're done here.
It's lively here.
Gen!
How's he?
Bring him outside!
What have you done?!!!
Look.
Qiguo! You got better!
There are two souls in his body.
One of them is very weak,
and the other one obviously doesn't belong there.
What's your point?
It could be that...
he is not your friend anymore.
Finish it!
What happened to Qiguo?
I don't know for sure...
A spirit trap is launching.
What?!
Get out!
A giantifying trap?!
He's gone?
Why run away, after we fell in his trap?
No way...
What happened?
You guys shrinked...
It's my fault...
Of course not.
I wasn't cautious.
How could he set up such a strong trap?
Why am I not shrinked?
Yours is a fairy body.
These traps only affect material sprites.
Soul Wind Mountain
And how will you turn back?
It will wear off after some time.
But I don't know exactly, when.
And Qiguo?
What if he's already...?
The two souls depend on each other.
Qiguo must be still alive.
Are you sure?
But we need to hurry.
We must find him quickly.
But he seemed to be so strong...
This trap wasn't set up just now.
It must have been prepared beforehand.
If someone could do this in a second,
it would be terrible...
He didn't attack when the trap got us.
Even if he has bad intentions,
he is still very weak.
Xiaohei.
Can you trace him?
Of course.
No need to take the trouble!
There's nothing I can't sense within 500 yards!
Sense!
He's out of range...
Who would run away within 500 yards?
It's my turn.
We must hurry.
What are you waiting for?
I can't summon Xiaolong...
Now you'll see what I can do!
Here comes the king of the jungle!
Is there another one?
It's okay, we can look for him slowly...
I'm counting on you.
Hei-shu!
You let loose a bunch of mosquitoes...
Shut up.
This way!
Wait for me!
What now?
I'll carry her.
You're so light!
Are you all right?
She was light a moment ago.
It's true we now weigh less,
but it seems our stamina decreased too.
Also we got a lot smaller...
One mile now feels like it was 20 times more.
We won't catch up by ourselves.
We should get something to ride on.
Got it!
It feels even slower...
The Heishus left us well behind.
I hope they'll soon find him...
Fairies never get tired.
Are you sure he stopped somewhere?
He's in a bad condition.
He needs a place to regenerate.
But no idea how far away.
A carnivorous squirrel?
We can ride it!
You just scared it away.
It's fast! Let's find another one!
Agreed.
How about that?
Is it fast?
Xiaohei!!
He'll give us a ride!
It'll be faster.
At least less tiring.
Let's find something else...
Agreed.
Same here.
That way!
Listen to me!
Gee.
A spirit space?
One-way gravity?
I'm pooped!
I can't go on anymore!
I'm not tired.
Don't compare a preteen human's flesh-and-blood body to a fairy's.
Let's get some food...
The Heishus can't find more traces.
What?
Let's eat first...
Gaping mushroom.
It gives you a terrible diarrhea.
Inedible.
Bud-sucking caterpillar.
Nutritious and really tasty.
No.
Cloud mushroom.
Hard as steel, used for making tools.
Inedible.
No.
Don't touch it!
Exploding chrysanthemum.
Pollen bursts out of it on touch.
It makes animals pollinate it.
But its fruit is edible.
Much faster now.
Thank you!
Hei-shu!
He left traces all along,
and there was always a next one.
But now there's none.
Then he must be nearby.
Now we need your help.
Did you find him?
I can feel him all around, though weakly.
He must have scattered his body.
Where is he roughly?
I'll force him to show up.
Are these the places?
Yes, I feel him at those places.
How did you know?
Stronger than I expected...
You're strong without being integrated to that body.
If you were in your own body,
I weren't a match for you.
So you realized it.
You didn't attack us when we fell in your trap.
I believe we are no enemies.
Can we help you with something?
Mind your own business.
The tree fairy who you possess,
will die very soon.
You want me to give my life up for this fairy?
No.
I'm offering you a tree type soul core.
This is a tempting offer indeed.
But my soul found this body
after three years of wandering.
I won't take risks again.
I guarantee the soul core is just fine.
I don't need it.
How could I make you trust me?
Immortal and Fairy
Why would I put my life
in the hands of a stranger?
Xiaohei.
If I can't persuade him,
I'll need your help.
It won't be easy.
You're right.
You leave me no choice.
You want to kill him?!
Strange... Where did this attack come from?
Now you can't scatter
nor regenerate your body, can you?
What have you done to me?
Weird question to ask during a fight.
Just so you know,
one more hit like that, and you'll meet your end.
What?
My spirit space!
It's rude to leave like this.
Let me go!
You let me into your space too easily.
That was a mistake.
If you are willing to leave this body now,
my offer is still valid.
I'll never accept it.
I can't force you.
What are you up to?!
The least that I can.
Send you to the next life.
So you kill him in the end?
Technically, no.
For you I can't do any more.
The fairy's as good as dead.
I know you won't do it.
Where do you get that baseless trust from?
I was just entrusted with this.
I don't want to lose the soul core either.
After all,
it's just a mere fairy.
Wait!
If I die, you'll stay like this!
You can't lock me up in your spirit space.
Especially that it becomes ownerless after you die.
All right!
I'll consider your offer!
It's too late now.
Farewell.
I accept it! I accept it!
Qiguo!
It's all right!
I've never thought you can move
to a plant within such a short time.
Should I destroy your new place, or will you appear by yourself?
Do you have to kill off everything around you?
You're exaggerating.
Could you please revert the magic first?
Otherwise I can't summon the soul core.
You just killed the tree fairy!
How could I believe you have a soul core?
You know, that tree fairy...
I've saved him.
Fenmo!
Qiguo!
How's this possible?
Unless...
He's space type...?
I must say you made a complete fool out of me...
We had to hurry, please forgive us.
What if I hadn't left that body even at the risk of death?
We'd be back at square one, wouldn't we?
We're back to normal.
Thank you.
You left me no choice.
A tree type soul core!
Do you really offer it to me?
Are you afraid it's a fake?
You wouldn't go that far
just to destroy a roaming soul.
I accept it.
I'm finally revived!
It's a good body indeed!
I've gotten much stronger now.
Are you not afraid I'll attack you?
You couldn't trust me first,
so I have to trust you first.
All right.
What's your name, son?
You can call me Gen.
My name is Muluo, I am an immortal.
You are Muluo...?
Shame on you!
You can't toy with our lives!
You're right...
I am ashamed of myself...
I take whatever punishment you see fit.
What will you do?
I don't know...
What would you have done?
I wouldn't have sacrificed Qiguo to save myself!
Of course.
But what if it wasn't Qiguo,
but those two ladybugs?
I don't know...
How can you say such a thing?
They can't be compared...
What's wrong with ladybugs?!
Nothing!
I think I'd have done the same...
Of course you wouldn't...
I have no right to condemn you.
If you want to make up for it,
ask Qiguo when he wakes up.
Sure.
It's best this way.
I leave things here to you.
You must leave now, Gen?
This is a mud ball I made.
This is my soul stone.
It's worth far less than the soul core.
But my spirit space abilities are in it.
If you ever need my help, you can call me with this.
I gladly accept it.
We're leaving now.
I will take care of the two.
Thank you, Gen.
We'll visit you when Qiguo's recovered.
We can go back too.
Sure.
Are you not angry with me?
I'm not.
You are a lovely little fairy.
Do you want to be my disciple?
I'll think about it.
Can we leave the fairies to him?
Of course, Muluo is a high-ranking immortal.
What if it's not really him?
I'm pretty sure it's him.
Was he wrong?
It's not so easy to say.
An immortal and a fairy...
Like a human being and a sparrow.
So a sparrow's life's worth nothing?
Of course not.
The immortal can be the sparrow, too.
Okay...
Prolongation of life always requires sacrifices.
So you don't want to live?
I'll cherish life even more.
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me